WOMAN: Babe, are you out here?
Yeah.
Thought you might be.
I have to go soon.
Okay. Okay, I'm comin'.
Come say goodbye to me.
- Coffee?
- Good call.
Would you make one
while I finish packing?
Of course.
(COFFEE MAKER WHIRRING)
Car should be here in a minute.
(TELEVISION CHATTER)
Oh, thank you.
(WHISPERING) Oh, my God.
WOMAN ON TV: West bound
is experiencing heavy traffic...
starting from the 610
Garret road exit
and stretching...
What am I gonna do without
your coffee for five days?
- They have coffee in London.
- Do they?
You sound really sure
for somebody who's never been.
Five days?
I thought you said four.
Yeah. Four days there, and then
I'm back on the overnight.
Oh, right.
You can still come, you know.
I can't.
I mean, there's somethin'
I'm tr yin' to untangle at work.
Oh, come on.
Just this once. Take a risk.
Next time. I promise.
Mm-hm.
This is a list of things
that need to be watered.
Thursday morning,
don't forget to leave your key
- for Mike and his son for the boiler.
- Right.
- (HORN HONKS)
- Mm.
Uh, those should last
until I get home.
Remind you of me.
Don't need reminding.
No?
Are you sure
you're gonna be okay?
I'll be fine.
Come on.
Love you.
- Bye.
(LAUGHING) Bye.
(LAUGHS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
- (LAUGHS)
- (SHUTTER CLICKING)
- Bye!
- Ooh.
(LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Good to see you, brother.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Uh, oh! What's going on, Chuck?
- Hey.
Hey, you, uh--
you just back from somewhere?
Across the pond, man. Everywhere
and nowhere. You know how it is.
Yeah. You just buzzin' in
and buzzin' out?
Yeah. I got a day
of security debrief...
and then,
it's the home base, man.
- Go kiss my little girl.
- Oh, that's important.
Yeah. I just said
goodbye to my wife.
Hey, man, what are you doing
for lunch today?
- Nothin'. No, no plans.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm completely free, man.
- That's great.
You know,
I got this computer shit.
Just a few, like, bits and bytes
I would love to get that
big brain of yours to decipher.
I swear, last time, bro,
you saved my life.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, of course.
- Oh, that's great. All right.
So, uh, you go ahead
and you eat your lunch,
then I'll come get ya?
- Yeah.
- My man.
Tick tock, tick boom, bro.
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Floor Minus Two. Operations.
- (SCANNER BEEPS)
- (BUTTON BEEPS)
Floor Minus Five,
Decryption and Analysis.
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
Hello. Are you there, Charlie?
What do you have for me today,
Señor Inquiline?
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
2. 1 terabyte tranche.
Kabul Station.
2014 to 2022.
Open this alone.
No charge this time.
How's the weather in Istanbul?
COMPUTERIZED VOICE: Nice try.
It's just a matter of time.
COMPUTERIZED VOICE: You think?
It's been five years, Charlie,
and you're still guessing.
CHARLIE: I'll get there.
I like puzzles.
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
Not as much as I like anonymity.
If I had to guess,
you're a 50-year-old
Russian man
living in Istanbul...
with an affinity
for Reddit boards
and Turkish coffee.
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
Perhaps, perhaps not.
I'm serious.
Be careful with this data.
It's highly compromising
for your agency.
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Hey.
Hi, Team.
Tell me again. How big
did you say the crate was?
Twenty meters by 10.
Another one
of Slater's hypotheticals.
Satellite images of a crate
on the back of a semi-truck...
rectangular in shape,
20 by 10 meters.
Destination?
A major metropolitan area.
- Mm. LA.
- Wrong coast.
Is the truck from Pennsylvania?
Mm-hm.
Headed to DC?
So far, so good.
- A flagpole.
- No, a missile.
Christmas tree.
The White House tree
always comes from a farm
in Lehighton, Pennsylvania.
And dimensions of the truck
tell the rest.
He can be really
annoying sometimes.
Wow.
(MAN SIGHS)
WOMAN: Oh, who's that?
MAN: The most dangerous
man in the building.
Secret agent. Bang, bang.
He and Heller are besties.
I'm his bestie.
No. We're just,
uh, acquaintances.
How do you know him?
Saved his life.
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Heller.
WOMAN: What are you wearing?
Sarah?
SARAH: No. Saddam Hussein.
He's dead.
Humor, Heller.
CHARLIE: Right, right.
I'm just calling
to let you know I'm here.
Right. I know.
I-I know. I tracked you.
SARAH:
I'd be hurt if you didn't.
I'm just grabbing a coffee.
Trying to keep me awake
a little bit longer
while I wait
for the rest of the team.
All right. Take a walk.
Go get some fresh air, honey.
But I want to lie down.
No. If you lie down,
you'll never get up.
Oh. Is that-- is that sage
advice from the world traveler?
Harsh.
Hey, listen.
I'm on to something here.
Can I call you later?
Yeah. I love you.
I love you, babe. Bye. Bye.
- Bye. Bye.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
(DISTANT CHATTER)
(EXHALES NERVOUSLY)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
(EXHALES)
What the hell?
REPORTER: There are witness
reports of a drone strike...
but U.S. sources have confirmed
that it was a suicide bomber.
The scale of the attacks
devastated...
REPORTER 2:
Some 150 people killed...
including French special forces.
Seven Danish marines were killed
in the explosion...
which was initially reported
as a misdirected air strike.
REPORTER 4: A Department
of Defense spokesman...
denied reports of U.S. Air
Force operations in the area...
blaming the attack
on local insurgents.
CHARLIE: Chief Moore.
(SIGHS)
Hey, buddy.
Carlos.
You okay?
You look like a damn ghost.
I was just rectifying some...
Charlie?
Some files.
Okay.
I may have looked somewhere
I shouldn't have.
Within our department?
Gray area.
We don't do gray areas, Charlie.
Our work is decidedly binary.
Then, no.
In that case,
what you do is you keep quiet.
Yeah.
(SCANNER BEEPS)
(LINE RINGING)
SARAH: Hey, I'm either busy
or dropped my cell
at the bottom of my bag.
Tell me who you are
and I'll call you back.
- (LINE BEEPS)
- Hey, it's me.
Um... Miss you.
I will water
the flowers first thing.
Call me.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SCANNER BEEPS)
- Chief Moore.
- Charlie.
I'm sorry, I don't see you
down here very often, sir.
Why would you?
Nice office you have.
Yeah. Yeah, if you don't like
sunlight or fresh air.
For a moss or a lichen
or mushrooms...
Charlie, have you been
tracking the news?
Well, I'm still tr yin' to find
an outlet I can trust.
That's what we thought
when we heard
you were here this morning.
We?
I need you to come with me
to the Director's office.
Please.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Floor Seven. Executive.
Director.
Director O'Brien,
this is Charlie Heller.
- Hi.
- Hello, Charlie.
Come have a seat.
I'd rather not.
Mr. Heller, I'm afraid
there was a situation in London.
Have you heard?
London?
An attack at the Christopher Street Hotel.
- Charlie...
- No, no.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Heller.
What?
- Your wife has been killed.
- No.
No, she's at a conference.
We should call her.
Charlie, I'm very sorry
to give you this...
Can we call her?
I have to call her.
Charlie, I think
you need to see this.
REPORTER: We're following
a breaking news story
here in London...
where a terrifying hostage
situation unfolded...
at the Christopher Street Hotel
earlier today.
Four assailants
stormed into the hotel,
taking a number
of individuals hostage.
Two individuals
sadly lost their lives...
including an American woman
who was taken hostage...
- It doesn't say it's her.
- ...during the ordeal.
Eyewitnesses report...
Charlie, you have
to believe us.
...a chaotic scene
inside the hotel
as the perpetrators
forced their way...
This is footage we pulled
from surveillance cams.
...terrorized the guests
and the staff
One of the victims
has been identified.
She is a 32-year-old
American woman...
that was tragically
taken hostage by the assailants.
The police are
not revealing her.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER AND SHOUTS)
It's all right.
I got this.
Don't worry about it.
- (OVERLAPPING SHOUTS)
- Charlie, Charlie, wait!
Charles! Charles!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS CONTINUE)
REPORTER: Metropolitan
Police has initiated
a citywide manhunt.
They are working tirelessly
to locate the assailants...
(CELL PHONE
RINGING AND VIBRATING)
...and secure
the rescue and release...
(RINGING AND VIBRATING STOPS)
...of the-- the hostage...
CHARLIE:
How can we not know more?
This was in London...
947,000 cameras.
They drove into traffic.
Nobody is getting
away with this.
You have my word.
Okay.
Tell me what we know so far.
Mr. Heller...
with respect,
let us handle this.
Forgive me, sir, I don't believe
we've officially met.
I'm the one who's gonna ensure
that those who did this
are held to account.
And what would that look like,
sir, with respect...
being "held to account"?
Look, we can't get
into specifics yet.
Of course, you understand that.
We'll tell you what we can
as soon as we can.
You just said
what he said, only nicer.
Go home, Charlie.
You need to take some time.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Subtitle
www.movieddl.me
(VEHICLE BEEPING)
- Next of kin?
- Yes.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SNIFFLING)
(SOBS QUIETLY)
(SOBS)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
- (KEY CLACKS)
- (OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTS)
(SARAH SCREAMS)
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
CHARLIE: The suspects arrived
via the service entrance
around 11:00 hours.
The vehicle had been
stolen overnight
at about 01 :24 in the East End.
Prints, DNA,
all professionally scrubbed out.
Four-person team.
Appears they had a meeting...
with Impact Investments
out of Indonesia on our radar.
This is when it all started.
Something must have
got heated inside,
it spilled out
into the corridor.
Impact's security
detail got jumpy,
and one of the four drew on him.
One dead, one critical.
Hotel security are alerted,
and the police have been called.
The suspects are now in a race
to leave the building...
and they decided
to grab some insurance.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(GUNFIRE AND SCREAMS)
Everyone! Get down!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTS)
Everyone down.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTS)
SARAH: Get down. Get down.
No, no, no. Run. Run.
CHARLIE: They only took Sarah
because she tried
to save someone else.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
GUNMAN: (DISTORTED)
You do as I say. Move!
(AUDIO REVERSES)
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
GUNMAN: (CLEARER)
You do as I say. Move!
CHARLIE: The man who took Sarah
is Mishka Blazhic.
Origins in Belarus,
though often based in Moscow.
(SCREAMS AND GUNFIRE)
They fled the conference room
with three hostages.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (AUDIO REVERSES)
MAN: Stay down,
or I'll shoot you!
(CLEARER) Stay down,
(GUNSHOT)
CHARLIE: This man, Lawrence
Ellish, is South African.
Ex-special forces.
Ellish seems to handle shipments
for the wider group.
Armed police
and security were arriving
from St. Pancras Station,
but were ordered to hold back
because of the hostages.
Police sealed off the area,
marksmen in position,
but the suspects are exposed,
and they knew it.
- (SIRENS)
- (INDISTINCT COMMANDS)
OFFICER: Armed police!
Drop your weapons!
OFFICER 2: Get down!
- (INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
- SARAH: Let go of me! No!
- (GASPING)
- (KEYBOARD CLICKS)
CHARLIE: Sarah's killer
is harder to track.
He seems to sense the cameras.
He says nothing.
But I processed all the CCTV,
cell phones...
dash cams, body cams...
and the audio to give us a 360.
And that provides us with an ID.
This is Horst Schiller.
Loose affiliations with dozens
of mercs and defense groups.
I'm still filling that in.
They seem to be
operating as interface
between bad state actors
and terrorist entities.
All business.
And they keep getting hired.
But for this one,
I have a current location.
Gretchen Frank.
Former Armenian IO.
She's in Paris.
Buys her bread at this cafe.
Turns up there regularly.
You knew this?
Thank you.
- We'll do a comparison.
- Wait.
You already know
about Gretchen Frank?
I understand you
wanna see progress, Charlie.
But sometimes,
the best course of action...
isn't always the most obvious.
"Most obvious"?
We want the whole network.
The network has nothing
to do with Sarah.
CALEB: But everything to do
with the sovereignty
and security of this country.
What you do is very important
to what we do, Charlie.
We think it would be good
for you to see Dr. Garrison.
Am I here for me or the Agency?
It is important we assess you're
well enough to return to work.
- Mm.
- Obviously.
But you've suffered
a terrible loss.
And we want to support you.
Can you describe your feelings?
Right now?
You mean, denial, anger...
acceptance...
Say more.
She's gone.
Yeah, that she had
to go like that.
And that I didn't speak to her
on the phone when she called.
And you blame
yourself for that?
Yes.
For not going with her
when she asked me to,
because I never do.
Never did.
And what is that
making you feel?
Uh, pretty useless.
A-Angry.
Very, very angry.
Uh, I gave the Agency
the names of Sarah's killers.
They did nothing.
- What do you want them to do?
- Their job!
I want them to go
after Sarah's killers.
Will that make you feel better?
This shouldn't be about me.
Sarah mattered.
She deserves more.
But in the end,
this is about you.
Sarah's gone.
You are gonna have to try
and come to terms with that.
I can help.
But only you can really
make things better.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SCANNER BEEPS)
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Floor Minus Five.
Decryption and Analysis.
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
MAN:
And the renovation schedule?
We can discuss
the cryptography project.
WOMAN:
Okay. All right. I can do this.
MAN: Thanks.
I think we need to flag this.
(PRINTER WHIRRING)
(PRINTER BEEPS)
(LAPTOP BEEPS)
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
You've been very quiet lately.
Guessed where I live yet?
(SCANNER BEEPS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
You good here
for a minute, buddy?
I gotta close up the back.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I--
I got you covered out here.
(CHATTER CONTINUES ON TV)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
Floor Seven. Executive.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CHARLIE: I'm holding the highlights
of over 100 eyes-only cables.
These are double coded
from a data cache
out of Kabul Station.
These are the official cables.
Same dates, same events,
except for very key information
that has been altered
or completely scrubbed
from the record.
What are you talking about?
This is your cover-up.
Have you lost your mind?
To put it mildly.
This is your order of operations
to destroy a hospital in Syria.
An allied base in Yemen.
An Afghani politician's house.
MOORE:
You have no idea what...
A border crossing in Somalia.
I count more
than 1,000 casualties
and over 400
civilian fatalities.
It's only out of respect
for your recent loss
that I'm not throwing you
out of this office.
I'm just gonna tell you,
you don't have a goddamn clue.
You see right here?
The convoy?
You targeted our allies.
You false-flagged it.
You got them all fired up
and then sucked them
right back in
where you wanted them.
You were forcing mission creep.
Okay. That's enough.
"That's enough"?
These were not
operational choices.
You, sir, made
political decisions.
And your signatures
are all over these.
Here and-- and here.
And here. Here.
You are so far
above your pay grade.
Well, you're right.
You're right.
Maybe we should...
take this up with the director?
Let her call it?
Or...
maybe it's for--
for the Times or the Post.
You've been
to the press with this?
MOORE: You'll go to jail, idiot.
Maybe.
But we'll all be there together.
- We have a mission here.
- Uh-huh.
A responsibility.
We'll defend our nation
by any means necessary.
I don't think
Mr. Heller came here
to debate ethics
and practices, right?
Right.
First, you need to know that
I've set up a dead man's switch.
If I don't code in
every five hours,
these files will
automatically be sent
to three top
investigative journalists,
along with a detailed report
and timeline of the events.
Twenty-four hours later,
the files will be
released to the public.
I get it.
We kill you,
Wolf Blitzer wins an Emmy.
No. Not just kill me.
You put me in jail,
you black-site me,
you extradite me...
you'll only condemn yourselves.
Then what the hell do you want?
He wants us to kill the people
who killed his wife.
No. No.
I don't want you to kill them.
I wanna kill them myself.
(STIFLED LAUGH)
- I beg your pardon?
- You heard me.
I want to find and kill
the people who murdered my wife.
(LAUGHS)
The CIA will train me.
I mean, this is
a practical joke, right?
I don't think you could beat
a 90-year-old nun
in an arm-wrestling match.
- (LAUGHS)
- That's funny.
Humor?
I want
mission-specific training
and all the information
the company has on these people.
Cash. And a new identity.
A legend.
- Anything else?
- (CALEB LAUGHING)
An Aston Martin?
A jet pack, maybe?
(LAUGHS)
I want a fighting chance.
(HORNS HONKING)
(DISTANT CHATTER)
(EXHALES)
(SNIFFS)
How do we know he really set up
the dead man's switch?
We don't.
We need to keep a lid on this.
Right.
So, let's play along...
till we're sure.
What? Actually train him?
What harm can it do?
Probably quit of his own accord.
Meanwhile, get Park onto him.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
We scrub his life
till we find the switch.
If it exists.
If it doesn't...
well, maybe there's
a training accident.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Let's use Henderson.
WOMAN: Escort team, stand by
for new arrival at gate four.
(HELICOPTERS WHIRRING OVERHEAD)
MAN: Charles Heller?
Charlie.
You're late.
With respect,
I'm actually about--
You're late.
You comin'?
The hell you doin'?
I'm not an Uber driver.
Sorry.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Okay.
- Put it over here on the left.
MAN: Yeah. Put those
two routers over there.
WOMAN: I got 'em.
MAN: The HDMI cables
are in the box.
PARK: My bet is he's bluffing.
CALEB: The man has an IQ of 170.
Let's not assume.
PARK: The only way out
is through security...
and there's not a chance he got
past them with a digital file.
Then why is he standing in
blind spots for over 40 minutes?
Here, here, and here.
On this day.
And look at that sweat.
PARK:
Yeah. That is a lot of sweat.
Are you my...
...handler?
I am Colonel Henderson.
My friends call me Hendo.
You will call me
Colonel Henderson.
I have been asked to give you
a refresher course,
even though
what you'll learn here
is outside
the normal curriculum.
Next to God Almighty,
I am the most important
person in the world
to an operative looking
to target enemy combatants.
Do precisely as I say...
and there is a slight chance
you may come out of this alive.
(CHARLIE CHUCKLES)
O-Only a slight chance?
I'm overestimating your odds
to boost your confidence, son.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please give us the room.
Go have coffee. Now.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
MAN: Yeah, make sure
you check for all spots.
MAN 2: All right, checking.
(ITEMS CLATTERING
AND CLANKING)
MAN:
Open all hard drive cleaners.
Bring the mountings too.
Wait. You think
he used a skimmer?
They don't work on these drives.
TECH: They work on printers.
Six days ago, he sent
the files to the printer...
and skimmed them
with a magnetic strip...
rewrote the software
in the printer.
Doesn't mean he got
the strip out of the building.
Okay. So, ANPR has his Saab at
Best Buy at 09:17 on the 13th,
where he bought
the magnetic strip.
Then got gas.
Copied the files at 11 :03...
met you two the next morning.
If he smuggled it out,
he did it here.
Still, screener
picked up nothing.
Maybe he swallowed it.
PARK:
Still would have picked it up.
(GUNSHOT ECHOES)
(GUNFIRE)
Kind of far.
You stand right there.
- Hold your fire!
- (GUNFIRE STOPS)
Try it closer.
Just a few rounds.
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
Did we test your vision?
Guess I just have
to get that close.
Yeah, at point blank range...
you might have a 50-50 chance
of hittin' something.
Overestimating my odds?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MAN: Why don't you guys check
the downstairs bathroom?
MAN 2: Pass me those boxes.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
So, an IED consists
of an initiator...
switch, main charge,
power source,
container for enhancements.
Stuff like fertilizer, nails,
glass, ammonia nitrate.
Beauty is,
you can use what you find,
big or small, as you like.
Improvise.
Design it for your purpose.
Carry the components with you.
HENDERSON: I'll be damned.
Looks like we finally found
something you do well, Heller.
May I keep this?
Sure.
CALEB:
He went here twice. This bar.
Why?
Once with Mr. Dominguez
on the night of the 24th.
Couple of weeks
after his wife died.
And then again,
the next month, the 13th.
The day he downloaded the files.
Right.
We searched it, though.
Let's search it again.
- HENDERSON: Name?
- CHARLIE: Clark Nicholas Jenson.
Spell that for me.
(STAMMERS) J-E-N-S-O-N.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Not Jenson Clark?
- No!
- Fast.
- Clark Nicholas Jenson.
- Where were you born?
Raleigh.
Raleigh, North Carolina.
- Which hospital? Now!
- Uh, Duke University Hospital.
- Your mother's maiden name?
- Uh, Deborah Jane Hammock.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Just a sec.
(PRINTER BEEPING AND WHIRRING)
It's all being re-swept.
Even the parking lot.
There's no drive here.
Okay. That's what
we didn't find.
But what did we find?
I don't know, this was
stuck under the jukebox.
Give me a quarter.
(JUKEBOX WHIRRING)
(ELECTRONIC BLIPS AND STATIC)
Pull the disc.
(DOOR THUDS OPEN)
(SIGHS)
You...
are not a killer.
No?
- Hey, who's this?
- Leave them.
Oh, these the assholes
that killed your wife, huh?
So, how do you plan
to take them all out?
The first one you kill,
you let the other ones
know you're coming.
And then what? What's your plan?
How are you gonna keep
the people
at Langley off your ass?
That's what I need
you to teach me.
(SCOFFS)
All right. I'll teach you.
Take it.
- Oh, come on.
- Go on, take it.
What is it? What are you...
- Take it! Now!
- Hey!
Point it at my chest.
- Point it at my chest!
- You think that...
- Do it now!
- All right, all right.
- Put your finger on the trigger!
- (EXHALES NERVOUSLY)
Come on.
Look at me.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
Come on.
- Come on, Charlie.
- (CHARLIE EXHALES SHAKILY)
Paralyzing, isn't it?
(GUN CLICKS)
Pointing a live weapon
at someone like that.
You have to either be
very confident or very stupid,
which is its own
kind of confidence.
Truth is you don't have
that kinda confidence.
And you are not stupid.
Not in the slightest.
You're just not a killer,
Charlie.
People have certain gifts.
You can't do what I do, no
matter how much I train you...
as much as you can't teach me
how to break code.
I can't make you into somethin'
that you're not.
I'm sorry.
When the time comes...
I'll pull--
I'll pull the trigger.
HENDERSON:
When the time comes...
you won't even remember
which end of the gun
the bullet comes out of.
(COMPUTER BLIPS)
MOORE:
How long is this gonna take?
With this encryption,
four or five hours.
CALEB: (OVER RADIO) What if she
can't break Heller's encryption?
MOORE: She will.
CALEB: How do we know
he didn't make 50 copies?
MOORE: We don't. (SIGHS)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
CALEB: Ali.
PARK: We're in.
It's a bluff.
He was playing us.
CALEB:
And he did pretty well, too.
Take him off the board?
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(GRUNTS AND SNIFFS)
Yeah.
Okay.
He's gone?
HENDERSON: He's got a bag
full of passports.
Even hacked the biometrics.
Yeah, he got out
on a janitor's card.
MOORE: This is a joke.
Maybe y'all misjudged
this individual.
MOORE: You think?
He knew exactly
what he was doin'.
Kept us chasin' breadcrumbs
just long enough...
while he got himself
some training.
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
Mr. Heller...
bugging a CIA officer...
is treason.
ANNOUNCER: Call for flight AA143
to London Heathrow.
(JET ENGINE ROARING)
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Ladies
and gentlemen, welcome aboard
American Airlines flight AA143,
with service
from Washington Dulles
to London Heathrow.
We thank you for your attention
whilst we demonstrate
the safety features
of the aircraft.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Yes?
Okay, you can open them.
(EXHALES)
Happy birthday.
(GASPS)
CHARLIE: Did it-- did it crash?
Apparently it wasn't
tied down properly
and got thrown around
in a tornado
or hurricane or something.
(CHARLIE LAUGHS)
SARAH: What do you think?
CHARLIE: I have no words.
- SARAH: Yeah?
- CHARLIE: Yeah.
SARAH: It's not crazy?
It needs some work.
CHARLIE: You think?
This...
This is the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Second most.
Happy birthday.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT)
...Paris will be departing now
from platform two.
- (OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
- (TELEPHONES RINGING)
He's in London.
One of his passports
just lit up at immigration
on his way to Paris.
- I'll grab local liaison.
- No.
This stays with us.
What about Henderson?
Call him.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(BELLS JINGLE)
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
Non, vraiment,
vous ëtes déjá fermés ?
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(DISTANT CHATTER)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
(PASSERSBY SPEAKING FRENCH)
(HORN HONKS)
- (KEYPAD BEEPS)
- (DOOR BUZZES)
(PANTING)
MAN ON VIDEO:
Hey, there, lock pick fans.
Okay. Today we're gonna pick
an apartment-style lock.
So, the first thing
we're gonna do
is you're gonna take
your tension wrench
and you're gonna
stick it in the bottom
of the keyhole and the plug...
just like so. Feel it?
- (DISTANT DOOR OPENS)
- (DISTANT CHATTER)
You're gonna apply just
a little bit of pressure,
just a little bit.
- Hey, you don't want too much.
- (CHATTER GROWS NEARER)
MAN ON VIDEO: Too much,
and what's gonna happen
is the pins are gonna
bind up on you...
and you won't be able to get 'em
up on a shear line.
And you're not gonna
get into that door.
So, gently, gently...
and feel it rotate back and
forwards, listening carefully.
Just a light touch.
All the pins are gonna line up.
And then, you're in.
There you go.
How to pick a lock.
(CHUCKLES)
Pretty darn easy.
Um... Yeah, don't forget
to like and subscribe.
Thank y'all. See you next week.
(HINGES CREAKING)
(FLOOR CREAKS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
(CELL PHONE BLIPPING)
(GASPS)
(EXHALES)
GRETCHEN: Moi, j'oublie tout.
Bon, je te prëte mes talons...
(GASPS)
(DISTANT CHATTER)
MAN: T'as oublié le pain.
GRETCHEN: La boulangerie était
fermée, tu te fiches de moi.
Tu veux mes talons pour alter plus vite
ou comment ça se passe ?
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(GRETCHEN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(GRETCHEN LAUGHS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(SPEECH GROWS DISTANT)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GASPS AND EXHALES)
(DISTANT CHATTER AND SIREN)
(PANTING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(HEAVY EXHALE)
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
CHARLIE: Bonjour.
Parlez, uh, anglais ?
WOMAN: Um, yes.
- Sunflowers.
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
All of them, please.
Tous?
The lilies as well, please.
I'll get all of them.
(LAUGHS)
You must have done
something really bad.
Not yet.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
WAITER:
Et voici votre café, madame.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MAN: Ça fait treize
fois que j'vous appelle.
- (MACHINES BEEPING)
- (COMPUTER BLIPS)
(COMPUTER WHIRS)
(TAPPING KEYBOARD HEAVILY)
Mademoiselle Frank. Je vous
pris de m'excuser. Continuez I'exercise.
Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
Je sais pas, Docteur,
y'a tout qui s'est éteint lá...
- Ça marche pas lá-bas ?
- Non.
Mais attends, viens,
on va alter voir.
- J'appelle IT ?
- Oui, appelle IT.
Excusez-moi,
le docteur Lessoir, il est oú ?
Vous faites quoi, lá ? Oh!
Ouvrez la porte !
Ouvrez la porte!
- (AIR HISSES)
- GRETCHEN: Ouvrez cette porte!
- (BANGING)
- (SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
(WHEEZING)
(COUGHING AND WHEEZING)
C'est quoi ça ?
It's pollen.
- (DOOR THUDS)
- DOCTOR: Mademoiselle Frank ?
Who are you?
Tell me where Horst Schiller is
and I'll let you out.
Screw you.
(AIR HISSES)
No.
- (YELLS AND WHEEZES)
- DOCTOR: Ouvrez la porte!
Mademoiselle Frank!
- (BANGING ON DOOR)
- GRETCHEN: No, no, no, no.
DOCTOR: T'as appelé les flics ?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais, Miriam ?
(WHEEZING)
No, no, no.
That's not gonna work.
Open the door.
I'm sorry.
Not until you tell me.
Please, just tell me
where he is.
NURSE: Ouvrez la porte!
Why?
Because you killed my wife.
Her name was Sarah.
Tell me where he is.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
- Tell me!
- (WHEEZING AND WHIMPERING)
Tell me!
I don't... I don't know.
- He contacts...
- (MUFFLED SHOUTING OUTSIDE)
He contacts us.
Messenger...
I can't hear you.
(MUFFLED SHOUTING CONTINUES)
Ouvrez la porte. Merde!
Shit!
(WHEEZING LOUDLY)
- (LOCK CLICKS)
- (BEEPING)
- (AIR HISSES)
- (GROWLS)
(CHARLIE YELPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING AND GASPING)
(BOTH PANTING AND GROANING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTS)
(BOTH STRAINING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(PANTING AND WHEEZING)
(EXCITED CHATTER)
- (CROWD SCREAMS)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MAN: Appelez les sec ours!
- (CAR HORNS HONKING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
MAN:Arrëtez-le ! Arrëtez-le!
- Il lui a pris son téléphone!
- WOMAN: Madame?
Madame, vous m'entendez?
(RASPING BREATHS)
(PANTING AND GRUNTING)
Shit.
Hello. Bonjour.
- MAN: Hello.
- Marseille, s'il vous plaît.
37 euros, please, sir.
(AIR BRAKES HISS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHURCH BELLS TOLLING FAINTLY)
What do we know
about Gretchen Frank?
Our people say one of her
own folks ran her down.
Most likely fallout from
when the London job went south.
I'll let State know.
French ambassador is asking.
Wasn't us.
(LAUGHTER AND CHATTER)
(MUFFLED DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES, LOUDER)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CROWD NOISES FADE)
(MUFFLED VOICES ECHOING)
(CROWD CHEERING, MUFFLED)
(DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES, LOUDER)
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER AND SHOUTS)
WOMAN:
Mais fais attention, abruti!
MAN: Hé, t'es fou!
(PANTING AND GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS)
(PANTING)
(MUFFLED HIP-HOP MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You want a beer?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Deux Heineken, s'il vous plaît.
How did you find me?
Phone you pulled
off Gretchen Frank.
- It's like a radar ping.
- Shit.
Doesn't matter
how smart you are.
If you panic, that will
always screw up a good plan.
Then there's
the survival instinct.
No one goes down easy.
And, of course, the aftermath,
when you realize you've done
something you can't undo, ever.
I can live with that.
You can't.
You surprised me, Charlie.
I can't tell you
how rare that is.
But it ends here.
There are no three-volley
salutes in this work.
We're the John Does
that get found in the dumpster,
if we get found.
Which you won't.
I'm sorry.
No, those were good lessons.
You're a good teacher, Hendo.
I took that into account.
Fifty-fifty odds, right?
Did you ever account
for the things I was good at?
Base charge on a timer.
(EXPLOSION BOOMS)
(PANICKED SHOUTS AND CHATTER)
(ALARM BLARING)
(ALARM AND CHATTER CONTINUE)
(DISTANT BELL TOLLING)
(BIRDS CAWING)
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
You have one new message.
(BEEPS)
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
Meet Ottoman Cargo.
Hangar seven.
They're expecting you.
You'll need 500 euros in cash.
ELECTRONIC VOICE:
You have one new message.
(BEEPS)
COMPUTERIZED VOICE:
The Fahri Cafe, Kuveloğlu Street.
I will pass you a book.
(DOOR SQUEAKS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Wait. He is not
who you're looking for.
Check your phone.
It was reckless of you
to come here,
whatever your reasons.
Listen, I need your help.
No. You have nowhere else to go.
That's not the same thing.
We're shopping, okay?
Give me your backpack.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
And your hat.
Now you look less American.
What do you want?
My wife was murdered.
I know about your wife.
And Paris, that was you?
I need to find the others.
No. Not here.
There is a parking garage
four blocks
from here, that way.
First floor.
Do some shopping, then
meet me there in half an hour.
And if you're not followed,
we'll talk more.
WOMAN: Tabii. Evet. Aynen.
So, how long has it been you?
Six years.
My husband was a CIA asset.
Former KGB.
He was Inquiline until he died.
He fell out of a window.
I'm sorry.
Accidental falls from windows
are the number-one cause
of death of former KGB.
You didn't know?
He taught me
everything he was doing...
how to mine data cache,
encrypt files.
And after he died...
well, I decided to keep up
my connection
to your department...
in case I needed help.
Which is why I always thought
you were a middle-aged man.
Because you were, to begin with.
You aren't exactly
what I pictured, either.
How did you picture me?
I don't know.
Mr. CIA-man-with-a-gun, I guess.
So, you'll help me?
(BIRDS CAWING)
(TURKEYS CHITTERING)
It's better
than any alarm system.
(CHITTERING CONTINUES)
This is the first place
I've stayed in
for more than a month...
in the last three years.
I don't sleep.
But I just don't want
to run anymore.
What makes you think
they won't find you here?
For that night...
when they do.
You really think you're gonna
fight off
the Russians with that?
It's not for them.
It's for me.
(KEYBOARD CLICKING)
INQUILINE:
Those are the three, correct?
CHARLIE: Yeah.
Schiller seems
to be the coordinator.
Ringleader.
But he's also
the most difficult to profile.
As far as I can tell,
they operate as middlemen
in the proliferation chain.
And just like the data
you showed me...
they also source mercenaries
for Director Moore's black ops.
Ellish sources the weapons,
but he's beyond paranoid.
So, we have to find a way
to pull him out of the dark.
Okay. Perhaps I can
start the conversation.
Suggest I have
a contract for him.
See if he will engage.
CHARLIE: Okay.
And this is Mishka Blazhic.
He seems to be based in Moscow,
but he likes
to keep on the move.
Enjoys his luxuries.
Travels everywhere first class.
He may be the weak link.
Even posts online.
This was just last week.
No location, but
the vineyard on level ground...
and the spacing
is wider than typical,
so probably hotter climate.
Chalky soil. Maybe granite.
Low sun hitting
the wine in his glass.
But the vineyard
would be angled north-south...
so it's sunrise.
And this church.
The architecture looks Spanish.
So, hot in October.
Maybe central Spain.
And here, in the reflection...
girlfriend, maybe.
- (SIGHS)
- (KEYBOARD CLACKING)
INQUILINE: And there she is.
Alexandra Solovoya,
who also likes to travel.
And she flew Moscow
to Madrid, last week.
We need to project everything
that makes America great,
but we need to do it openly...
We have to assume
he's still alive.
He has three targets.
O'BRIEN: And so, I pledge...
We need to locate
and get eyes on all of them.
O'BRIEN: ...this agency will be
worthy of the nation's trust.
Within our country and beyond,
we will be accountable.
MOORE: I saw your speech.
It was excellent.
You know,
you're the first person
my predecessor briefed me on?
About the stick up your ass
on ISIS, AQ,
Iran, counter terrorism?
Even now, three years
after mandatory retirement,
they keep looking the other way.
But it's housekeeping time...
and I need to know
where you stand.
Sounds like you're suggesting
it's time for me to go private.
Write a neat book about my time
with the company.
Yet here we are,
enjoying this lovely meal.
So, why?
Oh, please.
I'm new, but I'm not stupid.
I need you to be accountable.
To me.
Stop playing
your black ops in the sand.
I need to be across everything.
And I mean everything.
Hey, Brian?
Can you bring me
another one of these
sourdough roll thingies?
Sure, Mr. Moore.
- I'll tell you a story.
- Mm.
Your predecessor sat me down
at this very same table,
no more than
a week into his term,
and gave me pretty much
this exact same speech.
Oh, wait.
Maybe it was his predecessor.
I can't remember.
Anyway, I'll tell you
what I told them.
You have my full support.
Good.
Good talk.
Enjoy that pasta.
Where?
Madrid.
On whose orders?
Your lunch date.
Let's get someone
of our own in play.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
INQUILINE: Found him.
At the Aguilar Hotel.
Five stars. Nightclub.
Rooftop pool.
What?
Langley will be onto him, too.
Well, then we
keep tracking him...
until we have a clear field.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
CHARLIE: No.
I'm going.
Okay.
CHARLIE:
And keep an eye out for him.
This is who they'll send.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
Nobody walks home.
We roll home.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
He's a night swimmer.
He pays the staff
to clear the rooftop for him.
MAN ON VIDEO:
...the approval of the team
and the ambitious plans
were given the green light.
The sky pool
is suspended 16 stories
above the ground,
which is 70 meters.
The thickness of the clear glass
will be 420
centimeters in total...
made of three panels
with air gaps
to improve the strength.
The pool will be three
meters tall, five meters wide,
and can hold
an impressive 150 tons of water.
INQUILINE: (OVER PHONE)
You could shoot him from there.
You haven't seen me shoot.
Not for me to say here, boss,
but why bury him?
Why not just roll him up?
We're past that.
Too big of a stench.
Look, he practically invented
half of our surveillance tech.
Now, I will find him...
but you might have
a bigger stench on your hands
if he gives us the slip again.
You won't let that happen.
(WHISPERS) Charlie Heller.
- (WATER LAPPING)
- (CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
Okay. You're going to
have to clue me in.
Integrity.
It's all about integrity.
To have morals,
something like that?
CHARLIE: Yeah.
And something else as well.
If I have the math right.
I should move.
- (AIR HISSING)
- (GENERATOR HUMMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Hola.
- ¿Sí?
Can I confirm the pool
will be ready as usual?
CONCIERGE: Si, Señor.
- MISHKA: Gracias.
- CONCIERGE: De nada.
- Oh, my God.
- (CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MAN: Over here.
(DANCE MUSIC POUNDING)
Second stool down at the bar.
Yeah. What about him?
CHARLIE:
He's been following me.
I've clocked him three times.
Yeah, well, where there's one,
there's always more.
Shit.
You're right.
Yeah, I've got your man.
He's in the lobby, moving
across towards the elevators.
And the man at the bar,
I have an ID on him.
Charlie, he's also CIA.
You have to leave now.
Heller, are you listening to me?
No. No, we go as planned.
MISHKA: (IN SPANISH)
I'm allowed to use the pool.
I paid for it.
Is there a problem?
Tell me where
to find Horst Schiller.
(IN ENGLISH) Who are you?
You held a gun
to my wife's head.
She was terrified.
- You have the wrong guy.
- Yeah, yeah, I know.
You didn't pull the trigger.
So, tell me where to find him.
If this is a joke,
I don't get it.
It's not a joke.
This is a remote
that controls a device...
that's been
decompressing the air
between the sheets
of glass beneath you.
If I trigger it,
the glass will shatter.
So, tell me where he is...
or swim very fast.
You have the wrong person.
No.
I have exactly the right person.
(BEEPS)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(MUFFLED YELL)
(GLASS CRACKING LOUDLY)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Charlie, you should
get out of there.
(BEEPING)
Shit.
Henderson's headed your way.
Go towards the stairwell.
(CHATTERING)
Where is he now?
INQUILINE:
He's in the stairwell.
Three floors above.
Head towards the basement.
There's an exit in the back.
(CHATTERING)
- (ALARM BELL RINGING)
- (GROANS)
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
(ALARM BELL CONTINUES RINGING)
Shit! There's another one...
already in the basement.
He's coming towards you.
(GRUNTS)
Which way? Which way?
Left. Go left.
(CRASHES)
CHARLIE:
Where is he? The other one?
INQUILINE: I don't know.
I'm looking right now.
HENDERSON: Heller, stop!
Stop! Stop.
- (GROANS)
- (SHOUTS)
(PANTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
(METAL SCRAPES)
(GROANING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BLARING IN DISTANCE)
(BATON SNAPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SHOUTS)
(HENDERSON GROANS)
Ow.
(GAGGING)
(PAINED GROAN)
(GRUNTS)
(GAGGING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (HENDERSON SIGHS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
INQUILINE: Charlie, you gotta
get out of there.
You've got--
You've got to go.
Right now.
(DOOR OPENS)
You wanted to see me?
Have a seat.
Where's Charlie Heller?
As far as I know,
still on bereavement leave.
You talk to him at all?
We thought it best to give him
some space for now.
Makes sense.
I'll let you know
if we hear from him.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
(MUFFLED AUDIO)
CALEB: There.
- See that?
- Yeah. What's he doing?
His lips are moving.
Look in his ear.
He's talking to somebody.
Who?
TECH: Hotel security
was hacked yesterday.
CALEB: Right. Time?
TECH: 11 :07. It was a pro job.
The origination
is murky at best.
Istanbul, perhaps.
Talk to me.
PARK: From Heller.
"If I had to guess, you're
a 50-year-old Russian man
living in Istanbul."
CALEB: "lnquiline."
Code name "lnquiline."
Locate this person.
(CHIRPING AND CLUCKING)
- How are you feeling?
- Eh.
I don't know. I-I didn't
screw up so much this time.
Not so sure
that's a good thing, right?
Actually,
I meant feeding the birds.
When my husband was murdered...
I wasn't prepared for how quiet
the world would become.
All the sounds that
a person makes in your life.
The rhythms.
How you expect a certain sound
at a certain time of day.
The door, footfall.
The stupid thing he used to do
that annoyed me.
And then suddenly there's...
nothing.
It's just great...
silence.
For me...
Every moment since
has been about...
trying to fill that silence.
You need to ask yourself...
Doing all this...
is it how you should fill yours?
(WAVES RUSHING)
(TURKEYS CLUCKING SOFTLY)
FEMALE AGENT:
Code name, Inquiline.
Ex-FSB by way of the KGB.
Flipped to us in '04.
- Deceased in '17.
- Deceased?
The Russians suspect his widow
may be operating in his place.
Get me the Russian station chief
in Istanbul.
CHARLIE: What's wrong?
What's wrong?
I want nothing from you.
I just want to sleep
for one night
with another person beside me.
Okay.
(EXHALES)
(WAVES LAPPING)
(TURKEYS CLUCKING)
(GASPS)
(CLUCKING CONTINUES)
- (ALARM BEEPING)
- (MEN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
INQUILINE: Shit.
- Move.
- Shit.
INQUILINE: Go. Move, move.
This way. This way. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
(PANTING)
- (DOORS SLAM)
- (DOGS BARKING)
(WHIRRING)
(WINDOW SLAMS)
- (DOG BARKS)
- Hey.
(MAN SHOUTING
IN DIFFERENT LANGUAGE)
(DOGS BARKING)
(MAN SHOUTING)
(RAPID BEEPING)
(GASPING)
- (RAPID BEEPING)
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(GASPING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(DRONE BUZZING)
- (SHOUTING)
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- (GUNSHOTS FIRED)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- (SHOUTS)
- (GUNSHOT)
(MACHINE GUN FIRE)
- (GASPS)
- (GUNFIRE RESUMES)
(ENGINE REVS)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- (GUNFIRE STOPS)
- (GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(INQUILINE GASPS)
Have they gone?
It's okay. It's okay.
We're okay. We've lost them.
We're okay, we're okay,
we're okay.
(ENGINE REWING)
(GUNFIRE RESUMES)
- INQUILINE: (SHOUTS)
- CHARLIE: Shit.
- (ENGINE SLOWS)
- (BRAKES SQUEAL)
(GASPS) You're okay.
Shit. (PANTING)
(SEATBELT CLICKS)
Mm.
(SHOUTING)
- (DOOR SLAMS)
- (GUNSHOTS)
Shit.
- (TIRES SQUEAL)
- (ENGINE REVS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(PANTING)
Oh, God.
(LIGHT CHATTER)
(HORN HONKS)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(INAUDIBLE)
(HORN HONKS)
(MUFFLED CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE TICKING)
(COMPUTER CHIRPS)
FEMALE AGENT:
Heller's in Berlin.
MOORE: What?
This was 40 minutes ago.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES MELODICALLY)
(PHONE CHIMES)
- (PHONE BEEPS)
- Yeah?
CHARLIE: Put the money
on the chair. Count it.
Nothing until I inspect
the hardware.
CHARLIE: Hardware's right there.
Go ahead.
Stay on the phone.
Shit.
CHARLIE: You just armed an IED.
It's on a beam trigger.
You drop the lid, move away,
or cross the beam, it detonates.
Who the hell are you?
Do you honestly think
I came here alone?
CHARLIE: Look at the photograph.
See it?
Do you see it?
Yeah, sure.
I see the photograph.
CHARLIE: Do you recognize her?
London, maybe?
(VOICE EMERGING INTO ROOM)
That's Sarah.
You took her life.
For no reason.
Uh...
Wasn't me, okay?
I didn't shoot her.
CHARLIE: Fine.
Just tell me
what I need to know,
and I'll deactivate the device.
All right. Okay.
Come on, come on.
Where is he?
Schiller. Where is he?
It's impossible, man.
After what happened to
Gretchen and Blazhic, he's gone.
Horst's gone.
Well, then you are
of no use to me, are you?
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait!
He'll be at sea, right?
He stays on his boat.
- Which sea?
- I don't know. Russian waters.
That's 25,000 miles
of coastline.
- Which sea?
- I don't know! Russian waters!
Not good enough. Too vague.
Oh, come on, man!
You supply him with this shit,
right? These missiles.
- Correct?
- Yeah.
Yeah? So where do you
deliver them?
A port on the Baltic Primorsk.
It's there. Okay, there's a...
There's a café.
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
He calls in there,
and that's it.
How do you contact him?
He uses two numbers for his men.
If they get the right codes,
they know it's me.
That's all I have.
We'll see.
Give me your phone.
Your phone.
(CELL PHONE CLATTERS)
- (PHONE CLATTERS)
- The numbers are there.
The codes are by their names.
Their names?
Simon and Kristoff.
I'm not messing, man.
Simon and Kristoff. Come on.
- There. You see? See, I'm not...
- CHARLIE: You're right.
I'm not lying.
Now, deactivate this thing.
Hey, where are you going?
Where you going?
If you jump really fast,
you might survive the blast.
Please!
Wait!
FEMALE AGENT:
We got a ping in Rome.
MOORE: The little prick
is now at a museum?
CALEB: He's not in Rome.
We're chasing vapors.
How?
Because they're shoveling what's
left of Mr. Lawrence Ellish
out of the mud in Romania.
TECH: He just got
on a tram in Prague.
(SEAGULLS CALLING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You need to sleep again.
- (MACHINES WHIRRING)
- (JACKHAMMER RATTLING)
(DISTANT SHOUTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(HORN HONKS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(PHONE BLIPS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
Are you kidding me?
(CHUCKLES)
What do you think, man?
Just coincidence or what?
Yeah, somehow, I doubt that.
What do you say, maybe...
let's go get us a cup
of shitty Russian coffee, huh?
Come on.
Look at you
in the big, bad city.
Come on, let's go.
So, a rabbit on the run, huh?
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(BOTH SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Sit down, man.
So, you're here to kill me?
Nah, that's not really
what I do.
I mean, I might set you up
to get killed.
You know, facilitate it.
What are you looking for?
I don't know, my assassin?
Your assassin?
Yeah, and what do you think?
What does an assassin look like?
I mean,
it can kinda be anyone, huh?
even a slight little nerdy fella
- likes to work on computers.
- Mm.
Only thing dangerous
about him is
he's got this dream
about rehabbing a Cessna,
just to fly it around to prove
to himself that he's not afraid.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
These are killer, by the way.
Mm.
I'm gonna show you something.
Uh-oh.
(LAUGHS) I gotta hand it to you.
I almost didn't recognize you.
I said to the team, "Nah,
there's no way. That ain't him."
What do you want?
Honestly...
just here to save your life.
Oh.
How are you gonna do that?
Chuck, you killed three people.
Are you done?
Have you had enough?
No. I want the guy who pulled
the trigger. I want 'em all.
Damn, dude.
Well, that's
pretty cold-blooded.
You think they're gonna
let you leave Russia?
I mean, how does that even work?
How do you leave here?
The only way you leave here
is in a box.
But if you walk out of here
right now with me,
I can help you.
Nobody sent me.
I'm here on my own.
Shit, maybe you got a future
in this field.
Maybe we can figure
something out like that, huh?
- Just come home with me.
- (CHARLIE LAUGHS)
I have a future in the field?
Well, I could have sworn
you just said I have no future.
Look, I'm not gonna sit here
and pretend like
I understand
what's goin' on with you.
I don't, okay?
I've never felt that.
Your loss, I get it.
But you honored her.
What do you think she wants?
You think she wants you
to die here
in this country
with these people?
She would want you home, man.
No. I--
I can't go home.
Why?
She's not-- She's not there.
Okay.
You keep your head
on a swivel now, okay, Chuck?
Mm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
(MEN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Sir, I'm sor-- sorry.
Do you speak English?
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
Sorry, sir. I'm sorry.
There were two men.
With you on a truck.
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
- (MACHINES WHIRRING)
- (JACKHAMMERS RATTLING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
It's not very impressive, is it?
Placed near the cargo
you have below those hatches?
I think I might even feel
a little insulted.
- Who's coming after me?
- CHARLIE: Me.
- Me. I'm coming after you.
- Mm.
And who is running you?
What, are you afraid
Director Moore
has finally decided
to call it quits?
- Have you shut down?
- Mm.
Whatever you think you know...
I know Moore and Caleb
hire you and your outfit
to carry out black ops for them.
I have proof.
But, uh, that's not
what this is about, is it?
CHARLIE: No.
I came here
to face my wife's killer.
To look him in the eyes.
And tell him she mattered.
Sarah mattered.
So, it is just you. Hmm?
Gretchen, Blazhic, Ellish...
the men that, uh,
they sent after you.
This whole thing
is all your revenge?
Charlie's revenge?
(CHUCKLES)
Please.
I, uh-- I remember your wife.
She took the place
of someone else.
It's very, very brave.
I am sorry she died.
But it was...
necessary.
The police had blocked our exit.
I had to demonstrate
what would happen
if they did not allow us
to leave.
That-- That's it?
"Necessary"?
You are not
so different to me...
killing these people
to find your way here to me.
Has it made you feel better?
I won't know
till I've killed you.
It was...
- an instant. Your wife.
- No, it wasn't.
Yet you tortured
my colleagues...
dropped a man 16 stories...
suffocated a woman
in a-- a locked chamber.
You had them all unarmed,
defenseless.
Staged your elaborate murders
from a distance.
And you know why?
I do.
Because it's hard
to take a life up close.
You lose something each time.
A piece of yourself
you cannot get back ever.
And you've lost so much already.
So, you had to
give them a chance
to escape the mouse trap...
to run just fast enough.
Because then
you can tell yourself
there's no blood on your hands.
But doesn't mean you're weak.
Just means
you are not truly a killer.
Don't believe me?
(GUN CLICKS)
Go ahead.
You're here to kill me.
Take it. You'll see.
It's not a trick. Here.
All right, then. Huh?
End it face-to-face.
A friend of mine once told me
I'd never be able
to pull the trigger.
But he also said
I'd never be able to kill.
There it is.
That's what I came here for.
To balance the scales.
To make you feel what she felt
in that moment.
Before you killed her.
(EXHALES SLIGHTLY)
(BOAT GROANS)
Was ist das?
(SHOUTING IN GERMAN)
I've taken us on a detour.
Huh? Bullshit.
CHARLIE:
I've taken control of your boat.
We've just reached
Finnish waters.
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(COMPUTER BEEPING)
That is not possible.
This ship is a vault.
Your own CIA insisted upon it.
CHARLIE:
Using encryption I wrote.
Look, it's all running
from my hotel room.
These two may have
smashed my phone,
but they held on to theirs...
and my watch.
So, I'm the transmitter
and you...
you invited me in.
I just needed you to talk as
long as it took to get us here.
- (KLAXON BLARING)
- (SHIP HORN BLOWS)
That would be
the Finnish Navy and Interpol.
I gave them this location.
(SHIP HORN BLARING)
MAN: (OVER P.A.)
We are boarding your boat.
We are acting in accordance
with international law.
You are being placed
under arrest.
- (KLAXON BLARING)
- (REPEATING MESSAGE IN GERMAN)
Stand down, stand down!
Down.
(MEN SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
Heller.
Charlie Heller.
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
All right.
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
- (HELICOPTER RATTLING)
- (MAN SHOUTS)
(MEN SHOUTING IN DISTANCE)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(EXHALES)
When I took up this role...
I made it clear to everyone
who works in this building,
that even though our work
sometimes goes on
in dark corners,
that is no excuse
to allow darkness
to obscure our objectives
or our methods.
So, I'm deeply saddened
to have to tell you
that information has surfaced
that implicates senior members
of this agency
in carrying out
rogue missions,
which put the safety
of our own operators
and agents we work with
at great risk.
Gentlemen.
O'BRIEN: The cost of winning
the war cannot be our honor.
Those operations
were not sanctioned.
They were illegal.
And those individuals will face
the full force of the law.
I will now take questions.
REPORTER: Washington Post.
I understand these arrests
are linked to...
a series of killings
in European cities last year.
Was the CIA involved
in those operations?
O'BRIEN: You would not expect me
to answer that.
REPORTER 2:
NBC. Is the whistleblower
still employed by the agency?
O'BRIEN: I can confirm
that the officer is safe.
And that they will continue
to serve with the agency.
Who's the Uber driver now?
You must be
running out of lives.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
And you keep on
surprising me, Charlie.
Everything you taught me.
No, no. What you've done,
what you've become...
can't teach that.
I guess I just suddenly saw
what needed doing.
Yeah.
When no one else did.
Thank you.
(EXHALES)
See you around, Charlie.
(TAPS)
(ENGINE STARTS)